wickedhype.com 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy

**Third Party Advertising / Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. Security measures. We protect the personal information you share with us. Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

**Data Retention**  
WickedHype.com will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

**Linked web sites**  
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites. Children's privacy We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. WickedHype.com encourages parents to go online with their kids.

**Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:**  
Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. Look for Web site privacy policies.

Know how your child's information is treated. Check out the FTC's site(1) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

We may display advertisements from third parties. Third party ad-serving companies control which ads are shown. These ad-serving companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information from you. Advertisers use this information to target the ads and measure their impact. Third Party Advertising These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here. Third Party Cookies. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

It is our strict policy to never knowingly work in association with any infringing entity's unlawful use of a lawful trademark or lawful copyright. Remember, WickedHype is simply a site that provides its readers with reporting of urban media & DanceHall Reggae news and opinions.
